<resources>
    <string name="app_name">hackathon</string>
    <string name="title_activity_clinic">ClinicActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_reports">ReportsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scan">ScanActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_resources">ResourcesActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_article">ArticleActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_chat">ChatActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_resource_list">ResourceListActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_resource_details">ResourceDetailsActivity</string>
    
    <string-array name="article_title">
        <item>Determine your Skin Type</item>
        <item>Early Signs of Skin Cancer</item>
        <item>Essential Tips for Healthy Skin</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="article_author">
        <item>by Dr. Smith</item>
        <item>by Dr. Ling</item>
        <item>by Jillians (Msc)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="article_content">
        <item>To determine your skin tye, you can try this easy blotting paper test at home. Firstly, press a piece of blotting paper gently against your forehead, nose, chin, and cheeks. Then, observe the amount of oil transferred to the paper.\n \n
            &#8226; If there is minimal to no oil transfer, you have dry skin. \n\n&#8226; If there is significant oil transfer, especially in the T-zone, you likely have oily skin. \n\n&#8226;If the oil transfer is primarily in the T-zone, with minimal to no oil on the cheeks,the your skin is considered to be combination skin type.</item>
        <item>If you notice any of these signs, it is important to see a dermatologist right away.\n\n&#8226; A new mole or a change in the size, shape, or color of an existing mole. \n \n &#8226; A mole that has an irregular border or multiple colors. \n \n&#8226; A mole that is larger than ¼ inch (6 millimeters) in diameter. \n\n &#8226; A mole that is painful, itchy, or bleeds. </item>
        <item>Want to keep your skin looking its best? Here are the top 3 tips for healthy, radiant skin:\n \n 1. Protect yourself from the sun. Sun exposure is the leading cause of premature skin aging and skin cancer. Use a broad-spectrum sunscreen with an SPF of 30 or higher every day, even on cloudy days and wear protective clothing.\n\n
            2. Cleanse and moisturise your skin and daily. Use a mild cleanser that is appropriate for your skin type. Wash your face twice a day, in the morning and at night. Moisturize your skin after you shower or bathe, and again as needed throughout the day. \n\n3. Eat a healthy diet. Eating a healthy diet that is rich in fruits, vegetables, and whole grains can help to improve your overall skin health. These foods are packed with nutrients that can help to protect your skin.
    </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="skin_condition_name">
        <item>Acne</item>
        <item>Cellulitis</item>
        <item>Ezcema</item>
        <item>Hives</item>
        <item>Melanoma</item>
        <item>Psoriasis</item>
        <item>Rosacea</item>
        <item>Vitiligo</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="skin_condition_desc">
        <item>Acne is a common skin condition that causes spots or pimples on the face, neck, back or chest. \n\n Tips:\n\n  &#8226; avoid skin care products with alcohol \n &#8226; wash face daily \n &#8226;use an oil-free moisturizer \n &#8226; get enough sleep  \n &#8226; eat a balanced diet</item>
        <item>Cellulitis is a skin infection caused by bacteria. It can be warm, red, tender and very painful. \n\n Tips:\n\n  &#8226; keep skin clean and well moisturized \n  &#8226; avoid skin injuries such as cuts and scrapes \n &#8226; keep your nails short</item>
        <item>Ezcema is a condition that causes dry, itchy and inflamed skin. \n\n Tips: \n\n &#8226; moisturise your skin regularly  \n  &#8226; avoid hot showers \n  &#8226; stay hydrated \n  &#8226; wear loose clothing</item>
        <item>This causes itchy, raised welts that occur after exposure to an allergen. \n\n Tips: \n\n Avoid allergy triggers. These can include foods, medications, pollen, pet dander, latex and insect stings.</item>
        <item>Melanoma is a type of skin cancer that can spread to other areas of the body.\n\n Tips:\n \n The main cause of melanoma is ultraviolet light, avoiding sun exposure and using a broad-spectrum sunscreen can greatly reduce the risk of melanoma.</item>
        <item>Psoriasis is a long-term inflammatory disease that causes red, scaly skin lesions.\n\n Tips: \n\n Psoriasis is a long-term inflammatory disease that causes red, scaly skin lesions. </item>
        <item>Rosacea is a common skin condition that most often affects your cheeks, chin and nose.\n\n Tips: \n\n As we don’t know exactly what causes rosacea, it can’t be prevented.</item>
        <item>Vitiligo is a chronic autoimmune condition that causes the skin to lose melanin. \n\n Tips:\n\n There is currently no known way to prevent or cure vitiligo.</item>
    </string-array>



    <string-array name="medication_name">
        <item>Accutane</item>
        <item>Clarinex</item>
        <item>Clobetasol</item>
        <item>Differin</item>
        <item>Lotrimin</item>
        <item>Minocin</item>
        <item>Mirvaso</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="medication_desc">
        <item>Accutane is a medication primarily used to treat severe acne. It is also used to prevent certain skin cancers, and in the treatment of other cancers.</item>
        <item>Clarinex is an antihistamine used to treat the symptoms of allergies,  skin hives and itching in people with chronic skin reactions.</item>
        <item>Clobetasol reduces swelling, redness, itching, or rashes caused by skin conditions, such as eczema and psoriasis.</item>
        <item>Differin is primarily used in the treatment of mild-moderate acne, and is also used off-label to treat keratosis pilaris as well as other skin conditions.</item>
        <item>Lotrimin is used to treat fungal infections such as yeast infections, oral thrush, diaper rash, tinea versicolor, athlete\'s foot and jock itch.</item>
        <item>Minocin treats acne by killing the bacteria that infects pores and decreasing a certain natural oily substance that causes acne</item>
        <item>Mirvaso is used for treating skin of the face affected by redness due to rosacea in adult patients.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients_name">
        <item>Allantoin</item>
        <item>Bakuchiol</item>
        <item>Bentonite Clay</item>
        <item>Glycerin</item>
        <item>Hyaluronic Acid</item>
        <item>Kaolin</item>
        <item>Niacinamide</item>
        <item>Petroleum Jelly</item>
        <item>Tea Tree Oil</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients_desc">
        <item>Benefits: Moisturizes, soothes itchiness, and heals injured skin. \n \nFrequency: Can be used day in and day out. \n \n Note: Combining it with other exfoliants may cause irritation. </item>
        <item>Benefits: Wrinkle reduction, increases skin firmness, and minimise pores. \n \nFrequency: Can be used twice a day. \n \n Note: Glycolic acid might degrade the formulation.</item>
        <item>Benefits: Absorbs excess oil, exfoliates, and anti-inflammatory. \n \nFrequency: Once a week. \n \n Note: Can be drying in and of itself.</item>
        <item>Benefits: Moisturizes skin, smoothes skin, makes skin appear dewy. \n \nFrequency: Multiple times a day. \n \n Note: Generally safe to use with any products.</item>
        <item>Benefits: Moisturizes skin, reduces appearance of wrinkles, speeds wound healing. \n \nFrequency: Can be used twice a day. \n \n Note: There are no known negative reactions to hyaluronic acid.</item>
        <item>Benefits: Binds sebum, removes excess oil and draw out impurities. \n \nFrequency: 1-4 times a week. \n \n Note: Avoid using other drying agents.</item>
        <item>Benefits: Brightening, prevents signs of aging, reduces acne. \n \nFrequency: Can be used twice a day. \n \n Note: Generally safe to use with any products.</item>
        <item>Benefits: Seals in moisture, soothes cuts and abrasions. \n \nFrequency: Can be everyday. \n \n Note: Not suitable for oily, acne-prone skin.</item>
        <item>Benefits: Kills bacteria, fungus, and eases inflammation. \n \nFrequency: Recommeneded to use twice a day. \n \n Note: Must be diluted with a carrier oil such as jojoba oil.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>